AYUSH PRATAP SINGH

+91 9792757429 webdeveloper.ayush@gmail. com Antriksh Golf View Sector 78 Noida India 06/Oct/1997

Summary

I am a Frontend Developer, BCA graduate. I have been working for the last 1.5Years in the Web Development industry primarily Web Front-end & Web Apps Development. I am working as a front-end developer for the last 1.5years. I am extremely passionate about my work. In my professional career, have done 25+ projects. I have a strong grip on the latest front-end development technologies like Html5, Css3, Sass, Bootstrap, JavaScript, and React js.

Education

Delhi Public School

2016 - 2017

Higher Secondary School

Asian Business School

2018 - 2021

BCA(Bachelor Of Computer Application)

Experience

Steer For Change Foundations

Sep 2020 - April 2021

Frontend wordpress developer

I was working as Frontend wordpress developer all the sections and pages are developed by me.

Website - sfcfoundations.com

UI Cardio

Feb 2019 - May 2019

Frontend Developer Intern

I was working as Frontend Developer. My main purpose of this internship was to learn languages and to develop problem solving skill under the supervision of my seniors.

Live Projects

Portfolio Website

2021 - Till now

I have created my own portfolio website. It got all my small projects linked inside and my resume attached if you wish to download it will directly downloaded from there. With all my contact information.

Link - www.ayushchauhan.co.in

Weather App

Jan 2022 - Till Date

This web app gives you real time weather updates of any city in the world. Just type the name and see.

Link - https://comfy-palmier-fce625.netlify.app

Skills

Frontend Development, Landing Pages, Java Script, React. js, Bootstrap, Css, Version Control Git, Responsive for all devices

Languages

English, Hindi

Interest

Wordpress Developer & Manager

Others

Name - Introduction to Programming Using Python Url https://www.guvi.in/verify certificate?id=601c6z02K1L99kP 261

Name - IAB Digital Marketing and Media Foundations Certification Url https://learndigital.withgoogle.c om/digitalunlocked/validatecertificate code

Other Projects

Split Equally, Password
Generator,
Currency Exchange, To do List,
Coffee Store
Many more are mentioned on
my website.

Social Profile

LinkedIn:

linkedin.com/in/ayush chauhan0610/

Facebook:

facebook.com/profile.php?id=10 002 3532903004

Twitter:

twitter.com/mr_ayushchauhan